nyasatimes.com 2019-11-12

# Privacy - Malawi Nyasa Times - News from Malawi about Malawi

**Nyasa Times Online Privacy Policy**

Nyasa Times Online, and our parent organisation, the **NT Media Group** , guarantee that we will never, under any circumstances, sell, trade or make public your personal information, unless you designate otherwise. All personal information you provide will remain confidential. In addition, you always will have the option to edit the information provided to us or to have your personal information removed from our records.

**Traffic Data**

When you visit www.nyasatimes.com our systems collect basic information about your computer, including: IP address (your computer’s unique signature), operating system (e.g., Windows 95), browser software (e.g., Microsoft Internet Explorer, Netscape), Internet Service Provider (e.g., AOL). We also collect information about what you view on the site. This information reflects our readership as a whole and is used to help us better understand the Nyasa Times Online community.

**Use of Cookies**

Nyasa Times Online employs cookies — small text files placed on your computer’s hard drive — to track the type of content and sites to which our users link, the length of time they spend at any particular site and the Nyasa Times Online services they use. Cookies also help us diagnose problems with our server.

**Email Newsletters and “Send a Friend” Feature**

After signing up online, users will receive email newsletters and other occasional announcements from Nyasa Times Online. In order to distribute our email, we collect subscribers’ email addresses. We do not share addresses with other companies or partners. Users can unsubscribe from email newsletters at any time.

Nyasa Times Online offers a “send this story to a friend” feature, which allows our users to inform others about an article they might be interested in. For this feature to function, we ask for email addresses from the sender and for the recipient. We do not store or save these addresses and you will not receive any communication from Nyasa Times Online or its partners as a result of having used this feature.

**Discussion Forums**

Nyasa Times Online makes discussion forums available to its users. Please remember any information disclosed in these areas becomes publicly available, and therefore you should exercise caution when disclosing personal information.

If you have any concerns about the discussion forums, send email to [editor @Nyasatimes.com](mailto:discuss@alternet.org).

**Surveys**

From time to time Nyasa Times Online will conduct voluntary surveys of site visitors to obtain aggregate demographic information about them. This information may be compiled and shared in the aggregate with third parties, but no personal details will be traceable or associated with specific individuals.

**Linking to Other Sites**

Nyasa Times Online contains links to other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites.

**Children’s Guidelines**

Protecting the rights of children is important to us. As a result, we do not collect or maintain any information from individuals we know to be under 13 years old, and no part of Nyasa Times Online is intended to attract anyone under 13.

**Unsubscribe, Data Removal and Data Modification Policies**

Nyasa Times Online allows users to opt-out of receiving communications from us and to modify or remove their information from our system. The following options are available to do so:

  * Send email to editor@ nyasatimes.com

**Other Disclosure of Personal Information**

Nyasa Times Online will not use or disclose your personal information without your consent, except (i) as described in this privacy policy or (ii) as required by law, court order or as requested by other government or law enforcement authority. This policy does not protect information you post to any online discussion forum within our website.

**Contacting Nyasa Times Online**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site or your dealings with this website, you can contact:

Editor @nyasatimes.com

Nyasa Times Online reserves the right to amend this Privacy Statement at any time without notice, and only the current Privacy Statement may be deemed effective.

Follow and Subscribe Nyasa TV :
